I deleted my last post about Sean King because I realized that it brought pain
to some of my nearest and dearest loved ones who feel he is anti-Semitic. I don't know if he is or
not, but I will never let politics draw a wedge between me and mine. Y'all think this is a powerful
take. It is not. Politics should absolutely draw a wedge between you and yours when it is the
politics of oppression and supporting oppressive systems. So many of y'all fall short so often
because of your ignorance and because of your false altruism. It is not real. You know, I don't
even rock with Sean King like that, but what I don't rock with is this fake, you know, presentation
of I'm about my people. If your people are about the oppression of other people, they shouldn't be
your people and you shouldn't be protecting that. You shouldn't be there protecting their feelings.
Let me show you something. So many of you white people be showing your whole ass so often because
of your absolute fear of ostracizing any of your fellow whites for standing on the support of
others who are not. You're going to lose friends and being a real one. Yes. And they should not be
considered your friends. Why don't everybody know goddamn spineless?